Rukhsana Iqbal

Birmingham rukhsana2_pxv@indeedemail.com 07904 716 237

Organised and adaptable administrative assistant with three years experience working in fast paced office environments.

My attention to detail and excellent time management skills means that every task is completed efficiently and to the highest possible standard. I have a calm and patient disposition meaning that I am able to work effectively under pressure and focus on the task in hand.

I am proficient working in a team, but also work well independently. In my previous role, I was responsible for providing administrative support to the sales department reporting directly to the service manager. To succeed in this role i had to be exceptionally organised and demonstrate strong communication skills.

In my next role, I am looking to take on new challenges and additional responsibilities.

Work Experience

Additional Works Programmer

Interserve

June 2019 to Present

Daily management and progress of Work Orders through their life cycle to a stage of completion, in a timely manner to meet contract SLA.

- # Responsible for the processing of all additional, recommended and out of scope works requiring authorisation via the Client in a timely manner as per contractual timeframe.
- # Detailed planning and co-ordination of Work Orders with supply chain, internal operations and commercial teams.
- # Support of incidental works and other new works programmes.
- # Ensure that information of progression of Work Orders held on CAFM systems are recorded accurately and in a timely manner.
- # Ensure consistent full summary of audit trail of scope of works, quoted costs and completion details including paperwork are logged in CAFM system.
- # Liaising with Operations in the raising of supply chain orders, and the administration of subcontractors, including reviewing schedule of rates, with supply chain partners to meet service needs and contractual timeframes.
- # Working closely with the Contract teams to ensure reactive, and new works are priced in accordance within the contract.
- # Escalate, chase and resolve queries regarding Additional Works effectively within the specified time limit as per the process.
- # Assist Commercial Management in preparation of internal and external reporting of additional new works process and monitoring supply chain performance, with preparation for attendance of meetings.

- # Assist in the valuation and submission of contract Early Warning Notices and Compensation Events, maximising both revenue and profit margin.
- # Overseeing the delivery of work items by internal operations and supply chain ensuring adequate resources are available to meet established, programmed and additional new works services.
- # Ad-hoc duties as requested by Commercial Management and Operational leads.
- # Liaison with Client representatives, customers, supply chain and internal departments.
- # Development of positive working relationships with outsourced service supply chain.

Bridal Consultant (Weekend Job)

Wedding Dress Retail Outlet Ltd August 2015 to October 2019

- > Identify all potential customers and design all pricing strategies to maximize all firm profit and maintain customer satisfaction.
- > Supervise all product development trends and analyze requirements for all products and services for brides.
- > Provide efficient product demonstration to attract more clients and ensure achievement of all sales objectives.
- > Provide optimal level of customer services.
- > Assist all customers to select appropriate products and provide assistance on various new fashion and trends for brides.
- > Analyze customer fabric requirement and recommend appropriate material & analyze customers for all sizes and provide consultation on efficient shape.
- > Analyze all physical aspects of customer such as skin tones and hair color and recommend clothes and accessories and assist all customers to improve customer confidence.
- > Inform brides of all alterations to garments and process all payments for credit cards and cash and prepare documents for all customers.
- > Monitor all promotional events for store and resolve all issues.
- > Marinating and updating stock take.

Helpdesk Co-ordinator (Temp Assignment)

Mitie TSM - Birmingham February 2019 to June 2019

Comply with Health, Safety and Environmental policies

- Achieve the highest standards of quality, service and presentation of the business
- Effectively monitor delivery of reactive works and ensure contract KPI's
- Foster client relationships and develop a culture of trust and respect
- Allocate and dispatch reactive work orders to appropriate engineers
- Ensure work orders are completed to meet the contractual timescales
- Manage the relevant CAFM systems appropriately ensuring that sufficient information is captured for analysis
- Escalate potential unavailability work orders to the operations managers and supervisors
- Ensure that complaints are dealt with appropriately
- Ensure that labour resourcing is updated at all times that contains all the relevant contact details for their appropriate area

- Answer all telephone calls both internally and externally in a professional and timely manner ensuring that all messages are returned appropriately
- Manage all PPM activity from distribution to collation and closure
- Manage all contractors PPM activities
- Undertake any additional duties or responsibilities that are deemed required by the business in supporting the daily operation of the contract.
- Raise contractor orders and GRN where applicable
- Record Engineer/Supervisor Holiday records
- Raising of Quotes in the relevant CAFM system
- Undertake any additional duties or responsibilities that are deemed required by the business in supporting the daily

Branch Administrator

Rentokil Initial

August 2015 to January 2019

- >To deal with high volume of incoming and outgoing queries both internal & External
- > Dealing with invoices
- > Raising purchase orders on internal system
- > Processing contracts adhering to strict business policies
- > Processing negative transaction requests
- > Adding credits on the system
- > Manage large amounts of inbound and outbound calls in a timely manner.
- > Booking hotel rooms as well as ordering buffets for meetings
- > Maintaining and updating different databases
- > Liaising with different branches
- ➤ Project Management
- > Using Google Data Bases & Record Information Efficiently
- > Supporting Operations & Sales Team
- > Completing Complaints
- > Dealing with internal & External Queries.
- > Resolving Issues That Arise In Day To Day Running
- > Generating Reports

Administrative Assistant / Call Centre

Birmingham City Council May 2015 to July 2015

- > Manage large amounts of inbound and outbound calls in a timely manner.
- > Follow communication "scripts" when handling different topics.
- > Identify customers' needs, clarify information, research every issue and provide solutions and/or alternatives.
- >Answering incoming and outgoing phone calls
- >Arranging and booking appointments
- >Updating contact details on Microsoft Excel
- >Photocopying, Printing
- ➤ Handling high volume of calls
- >Transferring calls
- >Creating mind-maps

Administrative Assistant / Receptionist

GAMES4ALL Ltd

April 2014 to October 2014

Six Month Temporary Contract)

- > Delivering exceptional customer service
- > Work efficiently and accurate in a fast paced environment
- > Able to multi-task and manage conflicting demands
- > Meeting and greeting clients and visitors to the office
- > Handling incoming/outgoing calls, correspondence
- > Typing documents, photocopying, scanning documents
- ➤ Scanning candidates cv's
- > Creating and maintaining databases
- > Registering clients onto databases

Shop Floor Assistant (Voluntary Work)

ISRA Feed The Poor

February 2014 to April 2014

- > Approaching customers and helping them with their needs.
- > Assisting the management team in maximizing store sales and profitability.
- > Manually operating cash till systems, including cashing up.
- > Describing and demonstrating in detail a product and its benefits to customers.
- > Assisting customers with inquires.
- > Displaying promotional materials for sales.
- > Dealing politely with customer complaints and resolving them
- > Replenishing stock on shelves.

Education

A Levels

Birmingham Metropolitan College 2011 to 2013

GCSE's

Parkview School

2006 to 2011

Additional Information

Key Skills

- > An organised approach and excellent time management skills.
- > Exceptional communication skills.
- > Ability to work well as part of a team.
- > Excellent Computer literacy and excellent typing skills.
- > Excellent level of English spelling and grammar.

➤ Accuracy and attention to detail